liveacademicexperts.com 2015-08-25

# Privacy Policy | Live Academic

**Privacy Policy**

We always want to make your experience on the internet as enjoyable as possible ad that is why we encourage you to use array of our services with full confidence knowing too well that you are fully protected. It is common that every company collects information from different Internet users before the targeted audience starts to us the website or a web application in question.

  **Your Personal Information:**

Live Academic Experts collect Information from you, as a user, to provide you with a customized experience as you interact with our website and use our services. We never disclose your personal information to anyone and we will never do so under any circumstance unless authorized by you. However, we may disclose the information where necessary. For instance, if the law will require us to disclose personal information of users of our service, we will be obliged to do so.

  **How We Use Your Personal Information:**

**Registration:**

During registration, our company will ask you to provide personal information, whose sole purpose is to set up your account with us. Essentially, the information you provide is the one that will be used to run and manage your personal account with us from the time you start working with us to the moment you decide to terminate your contract with us. We may ask you to provide your names, address, electronic mail address, telephone number and billing information for the sole purpose of managing your account. For instance, we will request for your billing information because such is required to manage payment and transactions across the system.

**Point to note:**

Kindly be informed that we do not share your information with any third party. We want to make sure you stay fully protected and that you have an assurance that you can use our services any time without ever worrying about breach of personal information.

**We May Share Your Information Though:**

Do not get scared. By doing this, we do not mean to put you under any threats or harm. In fact, the information shared is used by our company and partners when promoting our services. This is common if you signed up for some subscription on our website. It is important to note that the company will use this information for the sole purpose of joint promotions to assess the results of the promotion of the service in question. The partners are under no obligation to use the information provided, under any circumstance for any reason whatsoever, to use the information for any other purpose other than allowed.

We strictly keep information of the students and experts within the company. We never sale or provide student or experts information to third parties. For the Payments, we are using Paypal. Paypal itself take care of student’s credit card. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law.
